myhotelectronics.com 2014-12-01

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is very important to us. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and browse our website and how we safeguard all of your personal information.

Firstly, we never sell your personal information to third parties. As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your ip address, your internet service provider, the browser you used to visit our website, the time you visited our website and which pages you visited throughout our website.

We may use cookies to store information on certain pages, such as your personal preferences when you visit our website. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as the website search, daily blog or discussion forums. We also use third party advertisements on our website.

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our website, which will also send these advertisers certain information including your ip address, internet service provider, browser type and when you visited our website, and in some cases, whether you have flash installed or not. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your web browser settings.

If you have any questions in regards to our privacy policy or need more information, please visit the contact section, submit your inquiry and we will reply to you asap.
